JACK FLETCHER

4 Raps Green, Taunton Somerset · 07502868409

__dev@jack-fletcher.me https://www.linkedin.com/in/-jack-fletcher https://jack-fletcher.me/

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A versatile graduate with an interest in all facets of technology, with a commitment to designing and developing innovative solutions to a problem domain.

I am experienced in object-orientated programming, including all phases of software development including design, development, testing and debugging.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: C# (Three years), Python (6 Months) HTML/CSS (6 months)

Software Experience: Windows 10, Ubuntu Linux, Visual Studio 2017/2019, Docker, Microsoft Remote Desktop, MATLAB, Unity Engine, PyCharm, Visual Studio Code, Hyper-V, VirtualBox

Other: Have experience working as a programmer in an agile environment of two to three developers, leading projects to fruition as either the project lead or the technical lead. I Have soft skills in customer relations and critical thinking, learned through retail experience and academic research.

EXPERIENCE

2020-2021

Implementation Consultant

Synertec

I worked full time as an Implementation Consultant at Synertec. I used a proprietary programming language to develop routing rules and developed visuals for customer's documents based on customer requirements and continuous feedback. In addition to this, I liaised with other technical and non-technical teams to iterate on our products and development practices.

2016-2018

General Assistant

Primark

I worked part time as a general assistant for four to eight hours a week on weekends. As a general assistant I minimized customer complaints by providing exemplary service. In addition to this, I maximised sales by ensuring the shop floor was fully stocked.

PROJECTS

JANUARY 2020- MAY 2020

Necromancer Game VR

Technology Stack: C#, XML, Unity

A 3D Tower Defence style game, where you take control of a necromancer developing an army. As a solo project completed in a single semester, I managed the project and developed all game systems. I gained knowledge in development practices for VR and was able to ascertain different interactions with emergent technologies.

JANUARY 2019- APRIL 2019

PEC-Application

Technology Stack: C#, XML, Unity

A 3D Tower Defence style game, where you take control of a necromancer developing an army. As a solo project completed in a single semester, I managed the project and developed all game systems. I gained knowledge in development practices for VR and was able to ascertain different interactions with emergent technologies.

EDUCATION

2021-2023

Computer Science (MSc), Part-time

Staffordshire University

Currently studying here

2016-2020

Computing & Games Development (BSc), Full-time

University of Plymouth

Graduated with a 2:1 / Second Class; First Division

Courses Completed:

- Web Game Technologies
- Games Development Immersive
- Software Engineering
- Games Workshop
- Intelligent Systems
- Algorithms, Data Structures and Mathematics
- Computation Theory and Artificial Intelligence

- Interactive Systems Workshop
- Artificial Intelligence for Game Development
- Object-oriented Software Engineering with Design Patterns
- Machine Learning
- Industry Engagement
- Programming for Entertainment Systems

2011-2013

A Levels: English Literature & Language, Psychology, Classic Civilisation *Richard Huish College*

ACTIVITIES

 Took part in Jamfuser 2020 as part of a team, creating all game systems and leading development in 'Pose of Faith'.